<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Music Uncovered</title><description>Nonstop Music Head-Up Display</description><link>https://musicuncovered.github.io/</link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:55:31 +0100</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:55:31 +0100</pubDate><ttl>250</ttl><atom:link href="https://musicuncovered.github.io/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://musicuncovered.github.io/download/download</guid><title>Download</title><description></description><link>https://musicuncovered.github.io/download/download</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:55:18 +0100</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Download</h1><h2>Download for iPhone and iPad</h2><p><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/music-uncovered/id6475651086"><img src="https://musicuncovered.github.io//images/Download_on_the_App_Store_Badge_US-UK_RGB_blk_092917.svg" alt="appstore-badge"/></a></p><h2>Download for Apple Vision Pro</h2><p>Coming soon...</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://musicuncovered.github.io/privacy/privacy</guid><title>Privacy</title><description></description><link>https://musicuncovered.github.io/privacy/privacy</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 08:58:32 +0100</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Privacy</h1><p>This article answers privacy related questions about the <strong>Music Uncovered</strong> app.</p><h2>Main data processing in Music Uncovered</h2><p>The purpose of <strong>Music Uncovered</strong> is to listen to music and identify songs. For this purpose the app uses ShazamKit which is an Apple technology build-in into the operating system of your Apple device. It uses your microphone to access the input audio stream. As an alternative audio source it can also access the audio stream sent from your device to your Apple AirPods. In both cases the audiostream is converted into a signature. The signature is a compressed version of the audio stream which cannot be converted back to the audiostream. The signature can be compared to the known signature of music titles. For that purpose the signature is transferred to the Shazam servers. They try to match your signature with the signature of all the songs in there database. If they find a match, they respond with the song information which includes title, artist, album, release year and the URL of the related coverart. The app then loads the cover art from the URL if available and displays the information of the matched song on the screen. If you use the <strong>Once mode</strong> of the app this can happen a few times until a song has been identified. If you use the <strong>Nonstop mode</strong> of the app this will happen repeatedly.</p><p>The app automatically stops the <strong>Nonstop mode</strong> if the you leave the app, lock the device or if the battery level is too low. The reason for that is to not drain your battery too much and also mantain your privacy if the app is not used. For that purpose the app observes several sensors and operating system states.</p><h2>Other data</h2><p>Apart from the use cases described above, the app does not process, collect or store any data.</p><h2>Personal data</h2><p>Apart from the use cases described above, the app does not process, collect or store any personal data.</p><h2>Contact information</h2><p>You may contact us, if you have any questions regarding data protection, collection and storage of your personal data:</p><p>Roland Schmitz<br>Schubertstraße 30<br>52146 Würselen<br>Germany</p><p>Email: <strong>uncovered</strong> @ <strong>2rs.de</strong></p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://musicuncovered.github.io/support/support</guid><title>Support</title><description>Is it not working for you?</description><link>https://musicuncovered.github.io/support/support</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 07:58:49 +0100</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Support</h1><p>You may get in touch with us regarding all topics related to <strong>Music Uncovered</strong>. If you have</p><ul><li>Questions about the app?</li><li>Ideas for improvements?</li><li>Features requests?</li><li>Any issues with the app?</li></ul><p>Then, don't hesitate to get in touch with us.</p><p>Email: <strong>uncovered</strong> @ <strong>2rs.de</strong></p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://musicuncovered.github.io/about/about</guid><title>About</title><description></description><link>https://musicuncovered.github.io/about/about</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 21:07:04 +0100</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>About</h1><p>All about <strong>Music Uncovered</strong></p><p><strong>Music Uncovered</strong> is an app that listen to music around you and presents cover and song information in a fullscreen view which is updated automatically with each new song. It uses matching colors and a beautiful layout to implement a glancable song display which can be read even from some distance. For each recognized song it presents title, artist, album, release year and cover art if available.</p><p>As a user of <strong>Music Uncovered</strong> you can decide if you want to identify the music just once or nonstop. The idea behind the <strong>nonstop mode</strong> is to have the app running for example in a corner of your table and whenever you want to know which song is currently playing, just glance to the app screen and instantly see all infos about the song without the need for further interaction.</p>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>